Hello
Hello friends, hello welcome to all of you once
again in our today's video
friends, in today's video we will
tell you that if you too are employed at home then how
can you earn money without any investment,
yes you can also become a motor insurance
agent or health insurance agent for free
without paying any money, about ICICI Lombard
and today we will talk and tell
you how you can become an ICICI
Lombard agent online, so friends let's
start how to become one, for that you will
need your PAN card, you need 1000
cards and one educational
qualification, how much education do you have, for this it is
necessary to have minimum 10th pass, so submit, let's start,
open your browser, you also open your browser
and search here
ICICI Lombard Agent Form, I will
put its link in the description,
we can open it from there, you click on the
agent form, first of all
our website is coming in front of us, we
click on it and the
website Open
Talent Acquisition For will be in front of us, in this we
can do our work and  After clicking this mark,
you will see here that you want to go from
ICICI Lombard and be a
part of the ICC number family. Brother, you can also become
a part of the ICC number family.
You will see the form here.
First of all, you have to set it. In the title,
select Mr. Message or Miss, whatever your title is.
After that, you should not enter your first
name, post it in the group. You should enter your
last name. If your question is only one
name, then you can enter
Mr. Yadav Guddu in the last name or your father name or must first name.
After that,
you should fill in your address, whatever your address
is, here.
After that, you have to select your city.
If you are registering your daughter here, then
you have to enter it here. There are
many cities inside which you will not register here.
Either you have to enter it here.
After that, enter your pin code number in the selected hide.
If you do not want to register your pin code, then you will see the pin code number of your Aadhar card. You
can enter it and after that  Later, you have to enter
your mobile number. You have to enter your active mobile number. You will receive
calls on your behalf.
All the officials of ICICI Lombard will
contact you in the same manner and
you have to enter your mail ID.
You have to enter the email ID which is active
or who knows its password etc.
After that, you have to enter your PAN number. It is
compulsory to enter the PAN card number. It will
not be updated. Enter the PAN card number.
You have to enter your date of
birth which is updated year. You have to enter it here.
After that, you will be given the
education qualification. If you have done
plus two graduation in Britain, if you have just
completed your degree, then you have to select it there.
After that, you will select sales
experience. If you have worked in sales before, then
how many years of experience do you have. If you have any
experience, then you have to select it on nil. Otherwise,
you have to click on one year, two years, 300 years,
West Indies and
after that, you will see it.
First, we will highlight it and you will see this only.
Which product are you interested in?  You are interested in some product
but you want to fulfill it, you
want to do it in bike interest or health
or travel, you are thinking
that we will do it on motor insurance, then you have to
click on motor,
in customer help, then you can click on light
or you can click on time, you can
set the time for the work in which you have to work now,
after that you will see
a big option below, you should know whether you want to
work full time
or part time to become an insurance agent, if
you want to work full time then you have to do
this letter gra, and if you are doing a job
and want to work along with this recipe
then you have to set the office, after this it will
ask you to update all product and
service brother, this is what we are asking for, and
if we launch any of our services or products, then whether
you want to update about it
or not, then do
not do it like this, after that enter the
captcha code, you have to enter the captcha code here,
after that
before doing the assessment of Aditya Cement,
you have to tick on treatment service by citing here
and read Dhyan Singh  If you want to
take it then only you click on this form,
otherwise there will be any problem, then
its owner does not have its activity, we are
just telling you how you can become an agent,
read this point carefully,
all the treatment conditions about them,
this company will work in its way, what is
Pure Taurus, you will find it written inside it,
after that you have to submit, so I fill
my form and that is all for you,
friends, I do it on my phone,
click on submit, as
soon as you click on submit, then here
TenQ responds your request, totally
brother, the ICC officer will
either call you, he will contact you, you
can review the email and you must have also received an email, in that
all your information must have been
written, so
friends, you can become an agent of ICICI
Lombard like this, you can also become an agent of ICICI Lombard,
you can do it, right now the link is given to
you in the description, by clicking from there
you will directly open this website and
from here you can become this number twenty  You
can start working in One Insurance, whatever is
required will be taken back and you will be given complete
cover for all the exams, training etc. ICICI Lombard
officials will give you, so thank you friends,
thank you very much for watching the video.